<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer 2024 | Jongjin Kim Academic CV</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/tags/summer-2024/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/tags/summer-2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Summer 2024</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:4321/media/icon_hu7729264130191091259.png</url>
      <title>Summer 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/tags/summer-2024/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>STA 2014 Summer 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/teaching/sta2014_summer2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/teaching/sta2014_summer2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;principles-of-statistics-my-last-course-of-teaching-at-ucf&#34;&gt;Principles of Statistics: My Last Course of Teaching at UCF&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Summer 2024, I had the opportunity to teach &lt;strong&gt;STA 2014: Principles of Statistics&lt;/strong&gt; for the final time at the University of Central Florida. Unlike a regular semester, this was an intensive 6-week course, requiring significant revisions to the course structure. I revised the number of exams, adjusted the grading policy, and reorganized the lesson plan from a 1-hour class to a 2-hour class. Reducing the number of exams helped improve the course structure, with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chapters 1-2&lt;/strong&gt; covering introduction and descriptive statistics,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chapters 3-5&lt;/strong&gt; focusing on probabilities, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chapters 6-7&lt;/strong&gt; addressing inferential statistics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, I reviewed and revised the quiz and homework problems to better align with the class materials, which made the course more coherent and effective. I’m pleased that I successfully completed my last semester of teaching at UCF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;syllabus&#34;&gt;Syllabus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;selected-student-comments-from-the-student-perception-of-instruction-spi&#34;&gt;Selected Student Comments from the Student Perception of Instruction (SPI)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am grateful for the positive feedback from my students, which highlights the effectiveness of my teaching approach:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I appreciated how thoroughly he went over the material and recognized that it was a long class, giving us a 10-minute break in the middle. He was clear and concise, and when he could tell we were confused, he spent extra time going over examples. Overall, he&amp;rsquo;s definitely one of the best professors I&amp;rsquo;ve had.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I greatly appreciated the instructor&amp;rsquo;s ability to make complex statistical concepts accessible and engaging. His clear explanations helped demystify challenging topics, making learning both enjoyable and effective. His willingness to answer questions and provide additional support showed a genuine commitment to our success. Overall, his teaching style was both inspiring and practical, greatly enhancing my understanding of the material.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I appreciated the instructor&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm in helping students understand challenging topics. His teaching style was amazing and made complex concepts much easier to grasp. Overall, his lectures greatly enhanced my understanding of the material.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;challenges-and-reflections&#34;&gt;Challenges and Reflections&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the challenges I faced was having to leave Orlando and move to Virginia after this semester. Despite this, I was able to successfully complete the course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;spi-score&#34;&gt;SPI Score&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;pictures-of-the-class&#34;&gt;Pictures of the Class&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;flex justify-center	&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:4321/uploads/24Summer/students.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Student Image&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
